A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, National Affairs, Office of the Vice President, Office Files of Shirley Teper FA656
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, National Affairs, Office of the Vice President, Office Files of Shirley Teper
1970-1976
Rockefeller Archive Center
Teper, Shirley
Ford Foundation
FA656
0.76 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Arrangement
Arranged in series by file type.
Collection arrangement is as follows:
Series I. Chronological Correspondence, 1970-1976
Series II. Reports, 1971-1976
Series III. Subject Files, 1971-1973
Scope and Contents
Contains subject files, correspondence, reports.
Biographical / Historical
Shirley Teper worked as an Assistant Program Officer in the Ford Foundation's Division of National Affairs, Office of the Vice President for several years in the 1970s.
- Chronological Correspondence, 1970-1976; I
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 1)
- Reports, 1971-1976; II
  - American Jewish Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 2)
  - Center for the Study of Public Policy, 1971 (Box 2)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund, 1971 (Box 2)
  - National Opinion Research Center, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
  - New Thing Art and Architecture Center, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Race and Ethnicity -- A Research Agenda, 1974 January (Box 2)
  - University of Michigan, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Vision of the Future Papers, 1976 (Box 2)
  - West Virginia Housing Development Fund, 1972 (Box 2)
- Subject Files, 1971-1973; III
  - Personal Interviews, circa 1973 (Box 2)
  - Conference Notes, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - National Affairs Retreat, 1971 February (Box 2)